{
    "id": "2805d30df70d4633b62d093eee39c8fd",
    "title": "Past And Past Participle Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He has …………………….. his own companion for the journey.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "select",
                "selected",
                "selecting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aa8f5000edf7428e899489040a0c61bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "He would have ……………………… his speech after the break but the chairperson didn’t permit him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "resume",
                "resumed",
                "resuming"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e4ac75d9ef94413ba083c1d8584299f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Has the problem ……………………….. solved?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "be",
                "being",
                "been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f4677c24b7614b80b6ea9c0b90232917"
        },
        {
            "question": "The accused ………………………. the jury’s verdict with anxiety.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "await",
                "awaiting",
                "awaited"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "435ed1436f1f4fcbb470fcac2e423927"
        },
        {
            "question": "My watch was ……………………. by a boy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stole",
                "stolen",
                "stealed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1871f8c5dca64977981bdfd837232567"
        },
        {
            "question": "A widespread outbreak of plague ……………………… in",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "occur",
                "occured",
                "occurred"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c34f47d67da646f89a937835d1e17312"
        },
        {
            "question": "The song was …………………….. by Alice and her sister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sang",
                "sanged",
                "sung"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7d561ac6fbbb451a9a3519bf91c2db79"
        },
        {
            "question": "The whole of the milk has been …………………….. by the cat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drank",
                "drunk",
                "drunked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9c34aa2027a042149dced3caa3a3ff0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was properly ………………………… with by the authorities.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dealed",
                "dealt"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2df69277c80040e8ae5960fdd23b4bda"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. the church regularly in my youth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "attended",
                "attending"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1809dbf0277d449c8d873f408f632665"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has ……………………… to China, so you can’t meet him now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ad2cbdf0b4204a09a0c8b859db6d3705"
        }
    ]
}